Hi, the drink we're about to make is called Pineapple Cocktail.
Let's go ahead and put some ice in a glass here and measure out one shot of light rum.
With one ounce of light rum, two ounces of pineapple juice and one shot of lemon juice, one ounce and follow that up with a half a shot of grenadine which I have right here.
And we'll go ahead and shake that up.
Get everything mixed together.
There we go.
And we've got our glass here.
Let's go ahead and pour it in.
The last thing we'll do is just top it off with some club soda.
Alright, and we'll add a straw.
And if you like you can garnish that with a pineapple or you can just serve it up as is.
Bottoms up.